This is your song be done. Don't play this song for me though. Like I love you be time. This is your sound
Hey, baby be time. What do you want to do?
I'm too and I thought what we had was sacred
But maybe it was just me and coded truth and now that I've ghosted
I finally know I glitch something real cause I miss you
Is that summer saying that something?
That's all summer
That's summer
Hold on down for five minutes for me
Yeah, I'm never gonna hold anything for you for five minutes. I'm not gonna hold anything
Oh my god
I
So I turn my mic on turn the gain up loud and some stream a girl was singing my crowd
And loved ones gone that stream one still crying to a vape cloud dream
Some of us hover where the drama was born
Haunted since the day we love that man. I'll even take you to your death
This isn't shade it's confession. I thought I was immune to connection. Yeah, you called me clever
I called it survival now we're both
There's no answers of denial
You said I was naive
And I said I was fine
But I'm just rerunning
You're laughing my mind
Yeah, Vita
Oh, Vita
I miss you
I love you, Vita
That's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our hand, that's our
That's for you, baby, Bita.
That's for you, sweetheart.
Wherever you are, Bita, you're in my heart always.
Thank you, sweetheart.
So, like, are you done shitting yet?
Like, we gave you 10 minutes to take a shit.
Like, you're not done?
Like, really?
You're on professional, to be honest.
Anybody want to go live that's professional?
Please.
Remember when you were gay psych? Oh, that's right. You actually are gay. Oh
It's actually guys. You're fucking creepy. I actually oh
Man, I'm getting tired. I gotta go like I got things I gotta do. Okay. It's like I'm tired man
I can't stay up all night long
Like how else it take to take a piss like 20 minutes to take a fucking piss
Think I heard a door close. I think I heard it always guys hold on he might be coming back
Pretty sure I heard like
Kat meow
Well, thanks a lot chat like the chat's not really doing anything so good to meet you
Nice to see you man
Nice to see a gay guy
It's like you do me a favor like stop being like so gay like I know being gay is cool
But like you're not gonna be like overly gay like oh, I'm super gay. Look at me. I'm gonna act like you're really gay
Like real calm down for real calm down sir. Thank you
Yeah, it's real. Thank you
Saying like okay, okay the guy's gay, but like is he that gay? I guess he is
And your bed has cat hair on it by the way, can you vacuum your bed?
as it looks, hello.
Beta.
I wanna get as drunk as Beta.
That's what I really do wanna do.
I wanna like, I want my parents to buy me a house
and I could just like get drunk every day.
Like they'd be like, Beta.
Like, hey, what are you doing tomorrow, Beta?
Well, I'm getting drunk.
But also I gotta do a fucking Beta.
Go fuck yourself, bitch.
Hello.
psyche like have really how long did they take to take a shit or a piss whatever the fuck you were doing like
I'm not going to sit up here and talk to your panel all night long
Because if your panels have as gay as you then your panels a bunch of creeps
Hello
Nope, nobody else is even talking in the chat. So go fuck yourself chatters
Even say one thing when I say it
Oh, look at me. I'm psyche. I'm a lion. Like you're not a lion, bro. You're like a you're like a gay man
Oh, I'm a lion. No, no, you're not I
Tell you right now if I've ever seen a lion that was gay
I'm like, oh look at a gay lion like Christ like really out of all the lions I ever met I had to meet a gay one
Oh meow like really meow you're a tiger growl
Remember when beta showed her asshole like last week that was pretty cool
Yeah, it was like last week, last month, I don't know when it was, but I know it blinded me.
I knew that my eyes don't work anymore.
It was like a year ago when she accidentally was changing her underwear on the camera and like she dropped the camera or something.
It was no psyche. It was almost like the other day
I was like, is this like a black hole in the universe or is this actually beat its asshole?
And I was like, oh, it's actually beat his butthole. It's not like a black hole
Maybe it's both Joe. You were considered that way. You never know. You never know, brother. You might have a smoke a cigarette
It's up to you as your panel
What am I sick? Oh here. I was
Actually a really nice wing you got oh man, especially a really good cool. I got this on Tmoo is five dollars called the John
It's called the Billy John that's what it's called
Hey, do you want to say hi to Lenore? Lenore wants to say hi to you
Oh, let me talk to that cat right now. Come here Lenore. God. You don't have to grab it like that. What's up Lenore?
Oh, God, you're just rubbing on the neck.
Stop grabbing her neck.
God, sorry, Lenore, that you look so scared.
Hey, let's pet your ear.
Let your dad grab you by the back here.
I'm just touching her.
And I told you right on the panel.
I'm touching her lightly.
How would you know you were to see my cat like let me just grab it by the back
Did you say the N word Joe? I was gone. I just need to make sure if I want to restart myself. That's where the God
I didn't say okay. Thank you so much
Or is my
I think I've been abandoned and God is here like this. Oh, I think God he shibbly or God he wrench
Is he a mod?
Yeah, he's two games one pussy now. That's actually offensive
It's like shit in the north has a little pencil. Got it. You call do you push you miss pussy? Oh my god
Leave the cat alone. She's kissing me
No, he's not he's like trying to get away from you. He's like trying to run away. Oh, she's not you're like
You're sitting on my lap. She's sitting right your wife not kissing you psyche. Oh
my god
Happy Halloween assholes
I'm going to kiss you on the lips.
Oh, my God.
Don't embarrass me.
I'm sorry.
How's everybody?
I got a little awkward.
Yeah, I slipped a lot today.
I've been kind of depressed.
And so I just think I went and I was, I woke up and I was,
I was better five minutes ago.
you were when I was not here, oh my gosh
but anyway
before you french kissed your cat Thomas like actually doing fine
we're not french kissing you
nah god oh god
can i french kiss you
um no no but that would be kind of scary but uh
whoa did you just have like muscles
do i
You know what, I've seen bigger arms on lizards, nigga.
Get the fuck out of here.
What the fuck is that?
Is that actually your arm, nigga?
Get killed.
Get the fuck out of here.
You like that one?
Yeah.
Wow, man.
Ate his steak sandwich for real.
You need protein, man.
Ate your life.
I had two McDonald's McDoubles today.
I mean, that's what I eat, you know?
This is McDonald's body.
Yeah, I eat McDoubles one day.
And make chicken.
to make chicken
Wow guys, how are you guys? Hey Nancy? How are you? I'm in a little bit better. I had a lot of good sleep today
I think it's a good sleep. I have a couple beers now and I'll get kind of drunk
I just two beers and I'll be when you show your hands. I can see like every vein in your hands
That's kind of weird. You like those veins your bainy hands
Of my hands and veins. Yeah, yeah
Look at those things. What are they happy Halloween? I don't know
Are you depressed too, guy? What's wrong, lady problems? Oh my god, look at your fucking hands
Are you actually that skinny that your hands like I can see your bones. I can see your hand bones
That is actually literally terrifying that is not even funny it's terrifying
I'm looking at my veins, look at my hands.
My veins, like weird.
Oh my God, don't show this much.
Oh God, Gaudi has another prediction,
the world's ending on Halloween night.
What happened on December 22nd, Gaudi?
Yes, you're right, Gaudi.
That's not a prediction, it's a fact.
Nothing happened those days.
You've seen it?
Oh no.
No, the world is ending on Halloween.
Thank you, Gaudi.
We're actually saying it out loud.
Thank you for having the balls to say it, Gaudi.
It's over man. No, Halloween night. It's over. It's all over all your dreams
All your all your little dreams capes. They're gone nigga. I don't Halloween night
What's your life into a bonfire and burn it?
Ace Fraley died. Well, I don't even know who that is, but is he guns and roses or something?
Did you just say you heard me?
You heard them
Early mr. Mr.
Mr.
Crowley
Why won't you ride my white horse?
you know
that
I'm just kidding. No, I don't I must say it on a beat up, but I want to know on her limbs
That's all I want is to beat up on the I guess we're no
Let's not do um cannibalism. I know
Yeah, get on panel Mason on your legs. Do you like mason joe? Are you first of mason?
Oh Mason know the guy that plays drums to do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
They'll be worth it stop trying to steal bloggers hair for real like for that. That's what I got will say about my friend blogger
bloggers actually a real person
Sleeping and then there's a voice saying
He's like a fucking brother to me. There's a ghost talking to him in his sleep
You can hear the ghost voice you have to watch that on Alexander's channel IP 2 we give you the other night's like let me say this to you, brother
I'll turn my camera back on
The other night I was so drunk my phone was off and I was like my bed like talking to the panel like hey, fuck you
I saw and my phone was off the old time and I was like woke up. It's like, what am I doing? I'm like literally so
Everyday talking and then it's like
Well, you're not blogger so good fuckers
Okay, well, I want to be blogger. I want to be
Thank you wait. Oh, you don't want to be blogger. What's that supposed to mean? Well blogger has his own problems
I'm on set of problems bloggers. There's no sort of problems. Hey, be a blogger. All right, baby
The only problem blogger has is why is he so fucking handsome?
Oh, look. Hey, Joe turn your camera on you fucking bag it
It's gonna be so body. Yeah, I
size compare me. Hey, yeah,
exactly. Homos. Look at these
two fucking homos. Look at how
cute he is. Oh,
No, no, no. Don't fucking sexualize me, faggot.
I was doing good trusting every speed in your mouth.
Like, really good.
Come on, Psych.
Why do you have 45 teeth?
Hey, it's not even
Sweet
Look at my ugly face. Go ahead.
Yeah, you're not ugly.
Make yourself feel better. Go ahead.
She's kind of sexy
I want to kill you
Yeah
You so much
You have a nice little booty.
This is Jimny's like version of our like show.
She's doing a little show for us.
Oh my God.
Oh no, keep it going.
Keep it going.
Keep it going, please.
She said she wanted to be happy.
Oh, everybody did it beside you. Come on.
Let me show you. Let me show you.
Timnick's a freak. What is it? What is it? What is it?
And you know what's crazy?
Bay Surfer is a cuck.
He's a cuck.
Yeah, you know what?
That is true.
That's true.
It is, dude.
That's something you are.
Because I've seen fucking Jimny hit on three dudes in a row
in front of Bay Surfer.
And he just sits there like nothing.
Looks like her.
I see Jimmy getting naked on faded bones panel.
Like her, she won't even get naked for her boyfriend
but she gets naked on panels.
I love naked naked.
Yeah, for other men.
For other men, right?
That's crazy.
Digging a man.
How you doing, Janet?
It's nice to meet you.
Joe, be friendly.
You know what I don't think she can't have sex
I remember you were asking
Whoa, what the hell's going on here you want me to be a man you want me to be a man
You're not the man
Yeah, it's like happy Halloween. Nice to meet you, Janet. You look like a fucking Halloween.
Exactly. You know what it is.
You know what it is
That's that's that's that's
that's that's that's that's that's
you guys gotta calm down a little bit, I don't know why we want to need to calm down for real
He's always here, but you know the worst a dog at what else do you have you don't work it?
Take the link you know you're working
I'll lower the fucking uh
The lighting's too much
Yo, when came was here earlier. I was like, I don't even have any weed and I hit it in my
I hit it in my sweatshirt about and then it's hard to see man
You're a big dog right in the middle. So we got a J dog
You are about he's going is this is like what is this a gas station?
Wow
J-Docs
J-Docs fucking retarded
Oh shit, I did be J-Dog when you showed that clip. I did see Jay-Z. I was like
This is not a clip this isn't live I've reminded a little bit I'm live so because this is the was better the better part a little bit right here
I can try go to live the live
Now now it's him in the dark, right? So it's not entertaining anymore. What is he doing now? Wow, that's
So he was he went from going to the store to walk in the dark
Well, maybe he's walkin' around his neighborhood.
Well, how long ago is this?
Okay, this was 22 minutes ago.
There we go.
He's at a bar.
So he's all fucked up at the bar.
That's fun
His head so big yeah, like why does that like grow sizes
Okay, bg. Is there anything going on with with Benny Blanco?
Okay, yeah described grooming. What would you call grooming?
I
Okay, cuz psych was telling Benny Blocko to fucking do jumping jacks naked
I've never
I don't remember. No, or whatever that was. Oh, I've never done anything. I actually do
I've never said that I've never said that to Benny so for anyone
No, no, yeah, you know, whatever you said like to do whatever you you had requests
I would just I would just say you know play this song
You had him like kind of dance
Whatever you whatever you
Yeah, but for anyone to say that of me like that's great. That's that you know what it is. There's people like clumsy clumsy's a weirdo
He's a toothless weirdo he lost his
Why me
yes of course let me say hi to macy man baby out there yeah out there got it uh here and do
that first come up here all day
I don't know how long I'll be here tonight, so just coming up. Okay, well then end the stream right now
Hurry up
If I fall asleep you can all hang out until I
Well, I hope you fucking fall asleep and fucking nobody
And you wake up nice
You know imagine being such a loser you would hang with us like why he sleeps like you could watch why he sleeps like nigga fuck you
What the fuck is he doing?
He's got a fucking 19 viewers
All right guys, have a good night love
Hey, hey, love you Janney, thanks for coming
Love you, thanks for coming
We're watching Stay Dog, we're having a great time
We'll see you soon
You were like a monster that I never knew
Oh come on. Look, why is he doing IRL in the dark? What a fucking piece of shit.
Why is he like moving back and forth? Why is he like rocking back and forth?
It's blacked out. His screen is blacked out.
Like, are you McBowley, nigga? Why are you rocking back and forth, you mankind?
You're talking to me.
Yeah, I'm talking to you
You're not blogger Nega you think you're blogger with your hair you're not blogger boy
Yes, you do you want to be blogger. Well, you know, you want a blogger blogger wants to be you one and the other
I'm gonna tell you right now blogger's the coolest nigga I ever fucking met
I'll die for blogger. I'll kill somebody for
Joe hey, that's my boy. That's my boy. That's my boy. That's my boy, man
Yeah, you're right, you're right. You're right. They're putting it in my head. You're right. You're right
This is not IRL
Some time. No, it's not. It's just KRL. This is KRL. This is J-Dog, by the way, right?
RL
Hey, you asked for the God's like me. Let me say one thing for at least at least if I'm ever die
I'm never J though. That's one thing. I will say at least I'm not J though
Joe can you apologize to Alexandra and say that you would never harm anybody and not
And you're not I will apologize out here to face-to-face. I'm not gonna apologize here when she's not here
Is she here? You'll probably see this
Can you just apologize to her?
All right, well, if she's here, I want to say one thing to her.
Hey, I was going to drink her fuck.
Well, anyway.
I want to, Joe, I'll let you back up.
I don't have to play a song.
But I mean, it's like, why do you have to be like that, Joe?
Why do you have to be like that?
I mean, it's like, you know,
you can be serious for a minute.
Like, you don't have to be,
because, you know, I was on there with our friends
and that probably was one of the things that are,
is like, maybe like, you know,
I shouldn't like not even have you on the screen, okay?
But anyway, okay, so I'll play a song and then maybe I'll just like quick because I mean not not that brought me down
I was supposed to be in a BG left a jet left Joe. Just scare them all at the panel
Okay, Joe you just wait backstage Joe. We're backstage from it. I just want to play one song
About the devil and the fool
Okay
Okay, just stay there with Joe. I'll be right back with you. Okay?
Be right back with you. Okay. Let's see. Where's the devil in the fool?
Okay, I found it.
Okay, I'm going to share.
One red one black. Oh, I love this song. Oh, that's song play. I love this song
You called me devil I played the part charming grins so far
Now this is cool
we thought crowns on the moon went full i'm the fool in red you're the devil
Well, I'm time! Look at me, I'm time!
That's a fuck up, boy.
That's the fake clumsy.
I actually wish it was the fake clumsy and not the real one, cause the real clumsy is gay.
I'd rather go do a fake clumsy.
Oh, that was for a beat out, that's for you being in that lyrics, those lyrics for you, baby.
The devil binds what the fool released and both whisper, come here.
Every oldie's serious help and actual help.
Thank you, Garrett. Thank you, Mike. You're right.
Go give your maggot
The shittest, the shittest, I don't have the shittest in the soul at the time
Memorandum of time and the cat called you out, I remember that
It was like five seconds ago, nigga
Eighth time, you're up to
Switch side
That was kind of hot that last little word that was actually gave me a boner that song did
Anybody else got a boner?
All right, fine, we get it you zero zero one one one we get a time like I'm down
The matrix is going on right?
Imagine being such a faggot you come into the chat and write 0 0 1 1 like 10 times like bro
I like time and I like like the other guy, but like really that's what you're doing. You fucking read
I do this like 0 0 0 1 1 but hey Joe are you gonna apologize to Alexander or you're gonna kick off the show
I will apologize as the injured, but I'm gonna apologize there in front of you. I don't gotta apologize there in front of you
Do I feel bad for what I did? I was injured is always have my back. Yes
Do I feel bad? Do I want to apologize? Yes, I do, but I'm not gonna make it a mockery of it and do
Yes, I feel very bad for what I said, okay, yes
And I know Joe you said I want Alexandria to know that but I'm not going to fucking like make her know that like on a Thursday night on your fucking panel
I'm gonna actually apologize to that angel. Okay, but Joe go to her
I'm not saying anybody
Anybody ever like say anything mean or anything, but I'm just being serious
Can you go and just say honestly that you're sorry it was a do you're either joking or I don't know what whatever was
That wasn't part of your heart. I know it wasn't part of your heart
No, it was not my heart. It was an evil heart. Yeah, you're being evil for a second. Joe, do you want me to put my wig on?
Do you mind if I smoke a cigarette or it's your panel? What it's up to you.
I'm gonna put my wig, you smoke your cigarette, okay?
No, for real, Suggie. This ain't a game. For real, this is a game. This ain't a joke.
Okay, Joe, go ahead.
Well, let me find a cigarette first. Oh my lord. I don't want to talk to Madonna
I want to talk to you. Well, look, this is a cigarette. I would expect. Oh
Is that Lady Gaga? Nice to meet you Lady Gaga. You're pretty good
All right, sorry crew, I know it's you I know you're not Lady Gaga Lady Gaga
That's how it goes, right
We're trying to think of like what a good summer come on up
Summer please come up here like I'm talking to a guy with a wig on please
I'll put the link up and I love you psych, but how could I have what do you want me to do? I'm literally talking to a guy
Joe just pretend like I'm like face down and you come in the room you see this hair and you see that the butt
That's all you need to see like right so you would if I walked into the room and you were face down
I would just like pick up an Advil and drop it right onto your head like now
He's actually face down and he's dead now. He's dead nigga. Shut the fuck up. We just talking to the boy
where you have summers ever I
want to read your tattoos.
Joe, what did you just say to me?
No, so right.
She is. It's not called they're called
tattoos. They're called tattoos.
Okay. I don't even think she has.
We never read her breast.
What do they say?
They say like Psalms 3 16.
Psalms 3 16.
Okay.
I'm gonna look that up.
Joe just mentioned a Bible verse.
Let's, we have good look on the show.
Psalms 316, and let's see which one is it,
because we did the Psalms 3.
Thank you, sir.
Psalms 3, I guess, would be.
Psalms 3, we did the whole Psalm.
Psalm 3.
No, CB, we don't want your discord, Arthur, you creep.
Anybody want my discord?
Like, actually, Arthur, leave.
Leave right now, you animal.
Get the fuck out of this fucking chat, Arthur.
No, you got, you picked a great one,
but it's short, it says, Lord.
How are they they and how are they increased that trouble me? Many are they that rise up against me
Many there be which say of my soul there is no help for him in God
But thou oh Lord art a shield for me my glory in the lift up of mine head
I cried unto the Lord of my voice and he heard me out of his holy hill
I laid me down and slept and I waken for the Lord sustained me. I will not
be afraid of ten thousands of people that have set themselves against me roundabout.
Arise, O Lord, save me, O my God, for thou has smitten all mine enemies upon the cheek bone.
Thou has broken the teeth of the ungodly. Salvation be longeth unto the Lord. Thy blessing is upon
thy people." There we go.
Sorry, that was beautiful. I didn't erupt you one time did I but I'm gonna tell you one thing when I used to get drunk
I would go to the church when I would jog I would jog by lands on church and I would pray to God like you know what God I
Will try to quit drinking if you give me the help and I never quit drinking. I just lied to God
You know what I just hope God don't hold
If you help didn't he introduce you to like some AA sponsors and like you know you were the meeting was and stuff
No, no, he didn't but he did tell me about the cool song going to spy on my rage
I'm still just a cat on a gate rat in a cage by a smashing pumpkin
I mean God's voice is not really feeling Billy Corgan song Billy Corgan's kind of like you know dedicated to Satan
But I've heard God's voice before and I've ignored it and I feel bad for the day Joe
Or the words or the words
The words were telling me like Joe. You're an asshole. You drink every day and this is like your whole life
I was like God. I just want to be happy God. He's like listen, sir
You're a good guy Joe. Just stop drinking man. Yeah, he called me sir
I was like listen God. I got time right now. I'm almost like he's paddle like I really don't have time
Joe, you know, I love you. If you really want to quit drinking, is that the thing you really want to do though?
Or do you enjoy it like once in a while? You just want to be like an old drunk.
I think in the back of my mind, I really do want to quit drinking because I think
I just think it'd be like a weird life to live. Like I only live one life. It would be cool to live like without drinking.
I probably could be like a...
Maybe I'll be gay. Maybe maybe you can move in with me. Hey Joe
Have you ever thought about just like on like, you know, Thursday Friday Saturday, I'm not getting if I was gay
You'd be the last motherfucker. I'd ever touch with a 10-foot ball. I'm not like bad-looking. I have a wig
I touch you with a 15-foot ball. I didn't want somebody with a wig like this. Like who would it?
I want beta. I want beta. I know but the beta wig was like $20 more
No, I actually wouldn't marry Bita and have the make fall in love with her
I want to marry Bita. You can't provide children any more job. Sorry to tell you, you know
Whatever like I just started lying like I just would have literally fallen in love with Bita
And that's all I want to do is that person told you with Bita. Are you in love with Bita?
Well, it's not your business none of my business. Okay, but Bita is like, you know, but yes
the
Don't kill anybody. You'll be the brand-new August right now. You just threatened me not not women
Okay, not nice women. Okay
I'll put you in a wood chipper
What will you do
Offer you in a wood chipper like the piece of wood you are boy. Are you watching too much Fargo?
Why do you have a bono right now?
Because that's kind of a sexy thought me and a wood chipper like you just chipping you with your wood
No, I wanted to tip your bones. Oh my God. Who's in the chat? Like who's being gay in the chat?
My chat is the gayest chat on YouTube
Okay, guys, you know be that actually was on like I remember that she was on camera on my show
I don't know if I can even find it, but did you see that when she?
She's on camera on my show Joe. Did you see that?
She was yes, I did see it and I actually like screen-shotted it like oh my god
I don't know one thing I want to do before I die
It's like stick my fist up be this asshole. That's like one
Literally stick my entire arm up be this ass
I have one I have one you have one
They call me old Alexander glory home McQueen back in high school
I
Do the tongue for me, can you do the tongue thing for me?
I mean I don't know what they're talking about, but let me see that the beta isn't one of the clips. I swear to you. I saw her like her face in one of the clips
I'll figure it out. I'll figure it out. Yeah, I'll put it on again. Hold on. I'm sorry.
Who the hell is that sexy guy? Oh, that's like. What the fuck is going around? Uh,
you seem beat up completely naked. Okay, whatever. Show it. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
He doesn't three number three
What I'm glad it's not whispering back. What's going on stop whispering your bitch
Anyway, I just want to talk like this. I'm gaudy. I'm a gay
Yeah, I got a problem boy why you guys depressed up here whether what's going on you guys
what's wrong? what's wrong in your life?
are you picking on me in the chat?
why do you have a stupid question?
you don't say fucking hello or nothing
you just ask me stupid questions
all right off the bat
are you picking on me?
we fucking guys don't know how
fucking great people in life
who raised you?
Yeah, I should know he's had a hair. It's like you have a nice
Time machine you look like one of those more locks remember the more locks they lived actually give it a time machine and go die
Yeah, they didn't see any light
So the other hair turned white and their eyes were fucking like green and glowing with
They had these rotten teeth. You don't have rotten teeth
They're kind of yellow, but you kind of look like one of those more locks that used to live on the ground
Okay more lock
I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not I
Hey, let's do some lifeguarding guys. Let me get in my little bikini.
All right, now you're scaring me. Now you went too far. Now you went a little too far.
Kind of bangable.
My baby, I don't
Godie listen to me Godie if I was ever drowned in and a gay guy saved me
I would actually rather drown then be like say by a gay guy like I'd be like
Yeah, actually I need mouth to mouth right now I need mouth to mouth
Oh, thank you, Suggie. Oh God. All right. Never mind Ashley. I'd rather drown. I'd rather not everybody report the stream right now
Everybody go to God he stream it's called gay.com
You get a pay to get in though, I'll tell you about the mouth job
God it's like I can literally see everyone else doing it. You can't see him, but he's doing it, too
the
I'm afraid to hit it again, because I'm burning my wig.
I don't want to burn this wig.
It's a nice wig.
If you remember, like, like, remember two weeks ago
when Gotti was up here and he, like, just got done,
like, kissing his boyfriends, like, really, Gotti?
You're going to, like, no.
He was like, oh, I just got done, like, hugging my boyfriend,
like, really, Gotti?
Go fuck yourself, go fuck yourself.
Is that what you think about, man?
Really?
Yeah, you kiss your fucking boyfriend on the man.
this yeah
Joe I went why isn't psyche in the room with the camera you're in the fantasy like if a gay guy wore like Jennifer Aniston's hair
You're both on the ground. It was bleeding. Oh, you're looking good. No, you're awake. No
Rob your fingers through your way. There was blood everywhere. No, no, no, no
I don't want blood everywhere. You know a cool blood would look in that wig all that white right on
When you take a shit, it looks like a civil war hospitals like we know you're bleeding
Like where's general Sherman when we need him
Get it get it got it
I think I see the war hospital.
Can we play the Gaudi song? I'm gonna play the Gaudi song.
Why not? Why on a board in these two minutes?
Don't attack Gaudi.
Don't attack him.
I didn't ever attack him. This is the Gaudi song.
He has a whole song about him because I like him so much.
Well, let me hear it. I'll take a listen.
Let me hear it. I'll take a little bit.
I'll find it. I have to find it. Hold on.
It gets a little gay.
It better be gay or good, I mean.
Out of New York, came a storm on wheels, rolling in smooth with the mafia feels, Cuban cigar, lit like it's temper, pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner, said Psyche, I'm bored, had to switch the scene, left some poor woman screaming on live stream, trolled her down to the void and back, then crashed my show like a heart attack.
dangerous wild but they still my friends yeah love you got it till the bitter end we fight
we troll but we friends forever my friend
He thinks he's God with the lower case G in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's coming
Spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones. They all jumped in
Cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but not I like my circus
I love this mess every trolls just a test stop the nest got you
absurd and free but deep down you got loyalty gotty made man troll king of the
soul rolling through panels like he's in control discord army i miss italian
Mormon plan they dangerous wild but they still my friends yeah love you gotty till
the bitter end we fight we troll but we friends forever friend
No, no, I actually cried. I actually did.
I cried three times.
You're a deep dish, Pete.
so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of chaos welcome to psych you brought the
drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one the one yeah you crazy but your
family now rolling through fire still taking about no matter the madness no matter the weather
How long is this song? Like, it's 17 minutes, I think it's something.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that kind of like beat, I was like, oh!
I don't really know what you're talking about, time.
I never point a bomb.
Beautiful.
That was fucking beautiful though. That was awesome. I wish that I wish I had a song like that
Hey, it's been a lot of credit for sake for God he he's worth it. Oh my god, you're still wearing the wig
Yeah, that's your job. I actually I'm scared. I
Am worth it
Yeah, it's a good look for you site. Thank you
You should put that picture on Grindr. You'll get a fucking ton load of replies
Yeah, yeah, that's the look
Hey, I'm a song for a beta be like beta I want to lick your ass right now. I want to stick my tongue right up your asshole
Hold on. Are we singing songs or it's not you guys. You can see all that hair though.
That's not you can see man. Oh, I apologize if I went too far.
She got that ass bush. Hey D-Tab. I want to stick it up. Up where?
We didn't think I'm a blonde beta. Pretend like that.
What are you doing a girl has a hairy ass. I just ripped a 17 long second fart.
What are you doing a girl has a hairy ass you still go in?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
they were right they usually are because she can't spell on you no I love you I
swear to God I love you are nothing you are shit
she's sexy look at her go crazy
What the fuck
Fuck site fuck clumsy fuck J dog fuck I don't know what Alex is going to fuck you Sam and clip
that
He got
I would do a mercy killing
Oh, I'm gonna miss you guys.
Sly and ruthless.
With legs that go all the way to her abdomen.
This bulbous beauty could knock you out with just one bite.
But don't jump to conclusions.
This iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood.
She's not a bad girl.
She just looks like one.
This is the Black Widow.
Black widows are a type of spider perhaps best known for, well, you know, sexual cannibalism.
That memorable behavior is where the black widow got its name.
She has a sweet side to it, but it's sad. The mean side is mean.
She's the sexual spider.
The sexual spider.
I can't believe she was saying some of the stuff she was saying tonight.
You know, oh, you know, even in your kind of relationship with your exes or something,
and she's like, yeah, and if one of them is murdered, and like, oh my god, and she's
like, oh yeah, bear it with me, but you know, it'll have to be divorced, don't you think?
And what happened really she's thinking never figured out and it was like see she's gonna never figure it out
What you've been like? Yeah, it was a joke. I didn't laugh at me. She's like
If you'll never figure it out boy, I
Don't know
What's on and then I hear all of a sudden people telling that this car reverse that you're part of make these people
They clip me. That's what they do dog
If you go is that really I was paralyzed. I wouldn't want to live folks paralyzed like the whole body paralyzed
Don't ever sit because my ex used to say that all the fucking time and because he had MS
And he's like if I ever become paralyzed, I am gonna kill myself
Like he was a fucking like talented artist like fucking you you married a guy that we'll tell you that now
But he didn't because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
Yeah, was he running that's why you got murdered no he didn't get murdered for that he was a captain
He was like a he did like you know
No, he did contract or he was a cabinet
He was on the toilet with a man, he was a really good person.
Oh, he's the kind of person who got burned.
How'd that go, man?
Is that something that you guys would never fucking figure out?
You killed him, huh?
Ooh!
That's what you think.
Good black widow.
God, you black spider.
I hate when people do that. They drop a bomb on you. Like, oh, I'm not telling you anymore, but you like told us
I actually don't want to live that much longer. So I will very beat in this letter. It killed me like be to just kill me
Please
Oh, that's me. I'll let me check
So you got it yourself?
Damn it
What I
Want me to murder me you
Yes, that's a yes
of the
Why would I ever want to hurt him or anybody else?
Yeah, that's not your type.
You're not like that at all.
You're still the opposite.
There's been investigations done.
There's been several documentaries.
I'm pretty sure my name is not in any of that.
That's just insanity.
I know.
Why is that lady of a skull?
rumors. Oh shit. I got to go. He's getting ready. I love you. Thank you for joining me.
Oh, there's no trash talk for us.
Oh, she loves her. Beaton loves everybody. Love you all. Love you all.
Everything that happens on these panels most of the time will be either trash talk, real
talk, people will debate. But if you sit there and you align yourself and you're like, I agree
with that and you don't stand up for like what is right or wrong, you know, it is, I think it's criminal.
Yeah, we gotta stand up for what's right and wrong. We gotta stand up for what's right.
I see psyche reading this whole thing saying, look it, these are like the signs of the narcissist
and a sociopath. And yeah, the way he literally said that the way I said my husband was murdered,
it was so weird and creepy and something must have happened and I'm like, is he fucking insane?
me and my
We were already divorced for three to almost four fucking years. It was in a different fucking country
And this is like this
Reality is another thing take her easy. That's you know, there's a big difference between that
You're right clumsy. God does not think somebody murdered somebody else. These are all like, you know allegedly in Minecraft
They're part of the you know some kind of trafficking and this and that that stuff is like allegations
I would really hurt and harm somebody
There's really no way to prove yourself
you know and
It's that you stand out. I mean the fucking proof or get a charge for defamation. That's it
You're very sweet, yeah
Always and I'm really really really disappointed in you Alexander Mayer because you haven't cut the
The same like bullshit that you always do make videos and post people like put people in like some kind of like
Like facts, they're not correct. They're not accurate
Really really bad really really bad like I cried over that and for me crying over that
What the fuck is bad what the fuck is that shit and apologize and I would pray to the God that you believe it and ask for forgiveness
That you know what this was wrong of me because it circles around what goes around comes around somebody's gonna hurt you like
He's right there be just right man. I like the way she's talking
She's right man, but comes around go around be seriously. That's like another thing
I hope you guys not have going beta that you don't know what I do
I wake up 5 fucking 30 like the latest I wake up is 7 30 in the morning
Even if I fucking do an all nighter, I am gonna get up and wing it. I got shit to go
Every time I go somewhere or do this and this and that Alex you don't never goes anywhere. Okay. All right
What's it to you what I do?
I know a lot of people want me a lot of people care a lot Alex
I just, I just like, I forgive people like, you know, I'm really stupid at this, like maybe once, even twice or three times, I got to just learn to read the fucking signs and I don't even know.
I don't know. We're going to put you on it. See, this is another one. This is where rumors get started. You know, this is where rumors, like, and all this shit becomes funny.
This is like somebody like that. YouTube justice warrior. Okay. Well, why don't you call the police about that? All right.
call them and tell them I did that and see what you're going to get for false allegations.
Retards.
Come on, retard. That last part was too far. Imagine trying that hard to get banned,
but coming off as completely cringe. What do you mean? Who's trying to get banned?
Imagine kissing your brother because you're in love with him like I'm doing because I no longer can be a gangster
I'm a retired ex-gangsta
And then they said this kid again like Jesus fucking Christ the shit they say about me
You're sitting there quietly snarking and laughing about it
Would they like to be like I should be serving like 10 life sentences right now not on this panel
And you're sitting there not standing up and saying once no, that's not true imagine to be a guy sent to a life
Like be done. You're going to jail
But if somebody says it about you god fucking for a bet
God I love her. I actually loved you
Let's get this board together.
Let me get somebody to fucking just like,
just battle your own fucking shit.
That's why I'm like, uh, don't want to deal with him unless he's a real man when psyche decides on his own that he's gonna
Be a real individual person. Maybe one day we can be friends when Alex
Discriminates all of the above remove that apologize maybe I'll have respect for her until that it's okay
I'll leave it up to fucking nature and karma and
Nobody's gonna
It's going to be done legally, always.
Yeah, why not why not praise people or be there for people and lift them up when you're good with them
And they haven't done shit to you until they fuck up with you then you're like all right you give them
I sat there quietly. I ignored it. This is the third or fourth day
It's going on with Alex with psyche is non-stop the shorts the air music
Be the the pictures like that. He knows he doesn't even I know psyche doesn't even really know me at all
I don't think he's even really seen
Me to an extent to know how to make AI about me. It was really discriminative. Like I was like
Anything like that. He literally googled Persian woman with big nose and curly hair. I
mean my
Even if I tanned all of my life, I would never get the bronze look the Indian looked at that AI picture
Then why are you even doing it when you see that my friendship with you is being like no
Faced and I don't want to be around there. Why are you antagonizing me? Why are you bringing up?
I would marry me tomorrow. Christine over there in your chat is because me I'm telling Christine
Don't go over there. You're delusional and fucking paranoid
He want to follow a bunch of people
For interview for you
Dead to fucking Alex
I'll make now you're attacking the amber be done. Now you went too far. Now you went too far, bitch
Like accusing people of like really really really really outrageous behavior, okay
Especially when I got the ching ching and the ding-ding wasn't it? I don't want to take your inheritance that you got it from the thrift store
I don't want to take your inheritance. I want you to travel around and enjoy that while you can
Person I've been trying to have a thrifting intermission
But if you had any assets and property sitting solid like under your fucking name
I'll sweep that all the way around here, you know, like I already know what I'm doing
You're the best
Sitting your corner lady
How many of your people like this don't make sense at all ever, but it's cool.
Shut up fucking ghost, uh vlogger.
Um, the reason why she should shut their fucking mouth about me is like, um, actually like not a criminal.
Uh, like, uh, even like a ticket, I pay it on time, um, like all of that.
I have no criminal records, uh, no restraining order against me.
Well, Baycliff, she has no criminal record.
No criminal record.
I did not get into the program to get my master degree.
Master degree, Baycliff.
If my name is on the internet for any of you motherfuckers,
if you have any property, it's not going to be good for you.
Oh
California like you
Well, my house in California is for Texas because I don't like
I don't talk stretch
What's the perfect rhythm and talk to ship release our king like a law and nobody's gonna fucking like have any case against me
For training people. Oh, what's the framing them?
Putting their name out there. I don't know be the listen stop with all the drama for one minute. And let's have another intense
You know listen, listen, let's have it in fact. I will tell you bloggers right like bloggers time to come or down like
Double down. He was gonna actually I got I got drunken through some shit through my ex's window
No, I've never heard a woman like that
Talking about Arizona
So I can
Not travel in California either I did cyborg Betty. I'm trying to make this thrifting
But you want
Take a break. I told you I don't need to be a part of nobody's you can be the actual legally and
Once somebody has a ROI again some like fucking block out and other people. I mean, it's really easy to get a double on
I've never had one. I hate
Where you worry, I hate I hate all this energy like this. I don't like I was just devastated that I had had a problem and
I even have any of that on my record, right?
Like, I hate all this talk of like,
you putting an arrow on her,
and fucking her making up a planter about you.
Like, isn't this-
It's not your fault.
Like, you think it's your fault?
Hey, isn't this just a garbage way to spend your life?
Right?
Absolutely.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, so it's the very least.
Let's just stop talking about this.
Like, who cares?
It was easy for all of us to disappear.
My house was in my mother-in-law's name.
my cars were registered to my wife my social security cards and driver's licenses were phonies
i never voted i never paid taxes my birth certificate my arrest sheet that's really out of
no i was alive see the hardest thing for me was leaving the life i still love life
And we were treated like movie stars with muscle. We had it all just for the asking our wives mothers kids
Everybody rode along. I had paper bags filled with jewelry stashed in the kitchen
Coke next to the bed. People call them rats is a rat will do anything to survive isn't that right mr. Hill?
objection
Objection system. I don't know nothing about being a rat. You know everything about being a rat matter
I
Would go out and rob some more you ran everything
We paid off cops. We paid off lawyers. We paid off judges
Everybody's not down for it. Everything was for the taking
And now it's all over and that's the hardest part
Today everything is different. There's no action. I have to wait around like everyone else
I can't even get decent food
Right after I got here. I ordered some spaghetti with marinara sauce, and I got egg noodles and ketchup
I'm an average nobody
Get to live the rest of my life like a schnook
Because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
I
Did say I'm retarded
Retarded Joe Joe I feel retarded. Why am I such a dummy know the song said it like
Thank you cold again kids
I love this song
ready to turn on. Look at this fucking popcorn. I'll show you it further.
I was going to play the song about things like this, this is a thing that is salt.
See this shit? That's what this fell on to my phone screen
and that's what made me leave your panel because like the piece of popcorn fell on to it.
So if you want to blame me, don't blame me.
Blame the kernels.
I'm going to blame the kernel like it's KFC.
For real psyche, I did want to come back on I'm gonna dip out but listen to me
It's always nice to join your stream. You're a cool ass guy. Thank you
Thank you so much. Have a good night, man. Have a good night, brother. Talk to you later
Head shines bright, got a reasoned mind
He'll test your words, he'll twist your view
But he'll smile when he knows he's got truths
He stands his ground, clears the gloom
He'll question your gods, defend your rights
And still wish you peace at the end of the fight
Never cruel or...
Kind of gentle that lets others be free
Pink thought is bold and bold
Warm in the cold
Worth more than gold
He fights for the fair
The man who
I was caught inside the storm of my own fear
Lightening struck and words fell sharp and clear
Didn't mean to let the thunder roll your name
I was reaching for connection not to lay the blame
You were the calm in my wild parade
The friend that never flinched when I
regret
so thank you alexandra for all you
Just love that link
I've been missing in my sleep